It seems today that all you see
Is violence in movies and sex on TV
But where are those
good old-fashioned values
On which we used to rely?
Lucky there's a family guy
Lucky there's a man who
positively can do
All the things that make us
Laugh and cry
He's a family guy
- Mom, where's Dad?
- Over across the street.
He's collecting Cleveland's mail
while he's out of town.
Black guy mail!
Peter, you're just supposed to
pick up Cleveland's mail,
not go through it.
Lois, black people are
different than you and I.
And me, I find that hilarious.
Boy, Cleveland gets a lot of magazines.
Grape Soda Today,
Orange Soda Quarterly,
The Fruit Punch Reader.
Hey, what you got there, Stewie?
Ooh! Mustache Aficionado.
Wow, look at these men!
What class. What grace.
And all because of a little upper-lip hair.
Lois, I am gonna grow a mustache.
Then I'll have it made,
like the Monopoly guy.
Except when he goes directly to jail.
I wish I could tell you that
the Monopoly guy
fought the good fight,
and the sisters let him be.
I wish I could tell you that,
but prison is no fairytale world.
Hey, Rupert, what if the refrigerator
was a monster that talked like this?
I am a monster.
I am going to bite your fingers.
Here I come. I'm going to get you.
Ah! I don't want to play anymore.
Normal voice, normal voice.
The refrigerator can't hurt me. Okay?
Oh, my God, Dad! What's on your face?
Meg, it goes by many names.
Soup Strainer, Lip Whiskers,
and, until recently, Giant Horse Vagina,
but I prefer the term mustache.
Oh! I think it's sexy.
- I think it's gay.
- It's not gay, Brian.
If I'm gay, then Freddie Mercury was gay.
Freddie Mercury,
the lead singer of Queen?
He was incredibly gay.
He was not. He had a mustache,
which is practically like a wedding ring.
I imagine you're gonna be
much more of a stern father
now that you have a mustache.
Well, Chris, there may be more
lap sitting than there's been,
and I might answer
most of your questions with a story,
but mostly, my mustache tells people
that there is a 90% chance
that I am poorly educated,
that I keep upscale porn magazines
out in the open,
and that I listen to the Little River Band
with giant headphones.
Ew! That's the ugliest thing
the fat man's grown since that horse leg.
Hey, Peter, have you seen my... Ah!
Brian, I'm sorry,
but what do I keep saying?
Do not stand behind me.
Because I will get scared.
And now back to
One Tree Hill.
Dude, let me tell you something.
There is nothing that'll ever happen
in the rest of our lives
that's as important as
what's going on right here,
right now, in high school,
by these lockers.
I've got so many problems.
Hey. Nothing that can't be fixed
by staring at a lake.
High school is such a serious thing
These problems matter
God, these high school students
are lame.
I'm a freakin' baby,
and I'm cooler than they are.
What the hell do you know
about high school?
Are you kidding? These kids today
are so easy to manipulate.
If you plopped me
in the middle of a high school,
I could be the most popular kid
there in a week.
Really?
Would you care to place a wager on that?
Absolutely. What are the stakes?
Okay, if I win, and you can't do it,
you have to put your nose in Meg's hat
and take an eight-second inhale.
Okay, and if I win, you have to go online
and download that footage of
the dancing baby from Ally McBeal,
and you have to forward it
to all your friends with the message,
"Oh, my God,
look what I just found online!
"Isn't this the funniest thing
you've ever seen?"
- So, is it a bet?
- Yeah, fine.
- Kiss on it? Oh!
- What?
Wow, Dad, you're up early.
Yep, it's
a mustache kind of morning, Chris.
I watched the sun rise in my jeans,
jean shirt and jean jacket.
Gosh, mustache culture is pretty cool.
You betcha, son. I'm gonna make you
some hash browns for breakfast,
and then later I'm gonna take you down
to the whorehouse to lose your virginity.
- Would you like that?
- Would I?
Wow, that's a way better present
than that buff hamster
you got me last Christmas.
Dad, all it's done is run on that wheel
for the past three weeks.
Yeah, looks like it's in pretty good shape.
- Can I pick it up?
- I wouldn't.
Boy, you know,
I've always wanted to come in here,
and now that I got a mustache,
the timing feels right.
Wow, all this stuff looks pretty good.
- Can we get some salami and...
- Brian, Brian, let me handle this.
- Peter, what are you doing?
- Speaking Italian.
Peter, you can't speak Italian
just because you have a mustache.
Hi there.
Is this the Quahog Mustache Society?
Yes, it is. What's the secret password?
- Mustache.
- All right. Come on in.
Good afternoon, mustache wearers.
Don't forget to help yourself to the buffet.
There's spaghetti and meatballs,
powdered donuts and bubblegum.
- Point of mustache.
- The chair recognizes your mustache.
Have we discussed what to send
Wilford Brimley next month,
as it is the 70th birthday of his mustache?
Oh, I think we just send a nice card.
Just make sure it has a mustache on it.
- Point of mustache.
- The chair recognizes your mustache.
What can we, as citizens,
do about mustache awareness?
Good mustache question.
We have a new product
in our mustache catalog
that makes a great stocking stuffer.
We call it the Must-Stash.
The slogan is, " You must stash
your Must-Stash in the mustache."
That'll be all for today.
- Good mustache.
All right, dog, here we go.
Prepare to lose a bet,
'cause I'm about to become
the most popular boy in school.
Excuse me, pardon me,
are you the cool children?
- Yeah. Who are you?
- My name is Zac Sawyer.
I just transferred here from
Rich Expensive Car-Driving
Sex-Having High School.
- Whoa! That sounds awesome.
- No, it's lame. Everything's lame.
Wow, if he says one more cool thing,
he's in.
I wear long sleeve shirts under short
sleeve shirts under long sleeve shirts.
- Wow!
- Oh, my God!
- Oh, my God, you're so cool!
- You're so awesome!
You've checkmated my teenage cynicism!
Excellent. I'm a bigger hit with the kids
than Will Smith and his nice clean rap.
Whoo!
Ha! Ha!
I respect women
when I'm on a date
I take them to the park
or maybe a museum
And I only try to kiss them
if they're ready
Whoo-hoo!
What, what, what, what
I say what, what
Help out your mom and dad
by getting a job
So you can help pay for school supplies
Whoo-hoo!
Say ho!
Wipe your shoes on the mat
when you come in the house
Someone just cleaned that floor
Whoo-hoo!
Say what, what!
Ha! Ha!
Peter, don't you think
you're kind of letting that mustache
consume your personality?
Shut up, Brian.
I am part
of a very special community now.
People with mustaches
look out for each other.
Hey. Oh, hey!
- Hey!
- Hey. Jeffrey,
- Peter Griffin has a mustache!
- No way!
- Way!
- Ohhh!
I know!
Oh, my God, Peter, look!
McBurgertown is on fire!
It's out of control!
We need someone to man the other hose!
Hey, that guy has a mustache! Grab him!
We need your help! Take this hose!
Uh... Okay, you just want me to spray
the water at the fire and try to put it out?
He knows everything about what we do.
Of course he does.
Look at that giant horse vagina.
Help!
Oh, my God!
There's somebody trapped inside!
Wait. If I go in there, I could get hurt.
No. No, with great mustache
comes great responsibility.
My mustache!
No!
God bless you, sir, you saved my life.
But at what cost? At what cost?
- Peter, have you seen Brian?
- No, Lois, I have not.
Well, I haven't seen him
since this morning, and I...
What is that on your head?
It's a mustache, Lois!
What, you never seen a mustache before?
Lois, would you mind
calling the police or something?
Quiet, mustache!
Oh, my God! Peter, I know you're upset
about losing that thing,
but get a grip on yourself.
Let Brian down.
No. I'm not living my life
without a mustache.
Even if sometimes
my mustache has Alpo gas.
Mustache fart.
Hello, I'm looking for Peter Griffin.
- I'm Peter Griffin.
- Mr. Griffin, my name is Todd Meyers.
I'm the man
you rescued from McBurgertown.
Oh, yeah, you're the guy
who cost me my mustache.
What, did you come over here
to rape my daughter?
No, I own the restaurant.
And to show my gratitude,
I'd like to offer you a lifetime supply
of McBurgertown burgers.
Free burgers?
Oh, man, this is a way better offer
than the one I got from Helen Hunt.
- You wanna have sex?
- No.
No, no, no, no, no.
No. No.
Peter, you should really slow down.
You've already had, like, 30 hamburgers.
Shut up, Brian.
It relieves the pain of mustachelessness.
And it's working. I no longer feel the pain.
Come to think of it,
I can't really feel anything
on the left half of my body.
Really? That doesn't sound good.
Peter, are you winking at me?
Oh, my God, someone call an ambulance!
Doctor, what happened?
Is he gonna be okay?
Mrs. Griffin,
your husband has had a stroke.
The left half of his body
is completely paralyzed.
Oh, my God!
Peter, sweetheart, how do you feel?
Uh...
Had better days, Lois. Had better days.
Mom, it's been three months.
When is Dad gonna get better?
Chris, I've already explained this to you.
Your father had a stroke, and
it may take him a long time to recover.
Lois!
Bring me another beer, please!
Uh...
Lois. You mind telling me
what the hell you think you're doing?
- I'm handing you a beer.
- You are handing it to my stroke arm.
This is my good arm.
Bring the beer over here!
That's better!
So, I'm shaving last night
at this make-out party.
I took a bunch of pictures.
You can see them on my MySpace page,
along with my favorite songs and movies,
and things that other people have created,
but that I use to express my individualism.
I have a MySpace page, too.
Yeah, I have mine ironically.
Hey, why don't you guys get lost?
I have to talk to Connie.
- Hey, guess what?
- What?
That's what. No, but seriously,
there's something I want to
talk to you about.
Sure, Zac. Anything for you.
You wanna go out to Anal Point
this weekend,
see what all the buzz is about?
OMG, that'd be so awesome!
Sweet.
We're gonna have a real raging time.
Before you know it,
we'll be like an old married couple.
- Uh, Lois?
- Yeah?
Uh, Peter's getting in the car.
Uh oh, overflow, population
common group, but it'll do
Save yourself, serve yourself
World serves its own needs
Listen to your heart bleed
Tell me with the rapture
and the reverent in the right, right
You vitriolic, patriotic, slam, fight
Bright light, feeling pretty psyched
It's the end of the world as we know it
Stroke! Stroke! Stroke!
Stop mocking me!
Well, Brian, you've lost your bet.
I, or rather, my alter ego, Zac Sawyer,
am currently the most popular boy
at James Woods High.
Well, Stewie,
you got the best of me on this one.
Congratulations.
I guess you'll be hanging up your wig now.
Oh, no, Brian.
I'm enjoying myself too much.
Do you know that I've got a date
with Connie D'Amico
this Saturday night at Anal Point?
Ah! I've heard about that place.
Really? What's it like?
'Cause I have no idea.
Well, I suppose if you imagine it
like a parking space that you think,
"Gosh, there's no way
I'm gonna be able to fit in there,"
but then you fold in the side-view mirrors
and sure enough, "Well, look at that."
Well, in that scenario, it sounds like
I'd rather be the
parking space than the car.
Yeah, that's what I've always guessed.
I hate being all strokey.
This is all your fault, McBurgertown.
You and your delicious hamburgers.
I swear, I'll get back at you someday
for what you did to me
and what you did to Wimpy!
I would gladly pay you Tuesday
for a hamburger today.
If only there was some way
I could be like everybody else again.
- How long was I in there?
- About five minutes.
Why are we not funding this?
Sweetheart, that's incredible!
And it only took five minutes?
Five minutes.
I went in there, they injected me
with a little bit of that fetal crap, and bam!
Good old gambling man Peter.
And now I can take my revenge
on McBurgertown!
- Wait. What?
- It's their fault I had a stroke, Brian.
And I'm gonna sue them for it.
Peter, you ate 30 hamburgers.
It was your own fault.
Yeah, besides, Peter, those companies
have huge legal divisions.
- You can't fight that.
- I'll find a way,
with the help of my snarky cat lawyer,
Meowsy McDermott.
You've gotta be kitten me!
Ha!
This court finds
in favor of the defendant,
McBurgertown Industries.
What? Hey, come on, that's not fair!
Mr. Griffin, what did you expect?
They have 100 lawyers,
and you tried to bribe me with
a subscription to Grape Soda Today,
which I already have!
Case dismissed.
What did I tell you, Peter?
One man can't take on
a multinational fast food conglomerate.
Oh, yes, I can. This ain't over, Brian.
Those people are bad,
and I'm gonna prove it to the world.
How do you expect to do that?
Are you kidding?
I've tackled tougher jobs before.
Remember that time
I was Robin Williams' jumping-off point?
- Okay, religion.
- Religion! You kill me, I kill you,
we both go to Heaven!
Seventy-two virgins!
You might have to help me out
with the last 10 or so.
Because Mr. Happy gets tired. Religion!
Uh...
- Politics.
- Politics!
"Well, we're gonna come down there
and take all your oil." " But this is our oil."
"Yeeha! Well, here's my missile."
"Okay, take it! Take it!" Politics!
You know what,
I'm gonna take a five-minute break.
Five-minute break!
What are you, a construction worker?
"Hey, baby, I'm not gay! " " Does this
yellow hat make my ass look fat?"
Five-minute break!
Ow! Ow! Ow!
You enjoy the movie, baby?
Yeah. But I think
I'm gonna enjoy this even more.
No thanks, I am stuffed.
So are we just gonna sit here and talk,
or are we gonna do it?
All right, baby, those are the magic words.
Check out my penis!
- Oh, my God.
- Yeah. I am ready for sex!
I drank eight gallons of water today.
This baby's ready to explode!
Is there more underneath, or is that it?
I'm sorry?
Zac, just get the hell out of my car!
That's it? That was sex?
What a rip-off. I should sue her.
Be careful you're not
held in contempt of cat!
Ha!
Pardon me, we're two Asian businessmen
looking to invest
in McBurgertown Industries,
and we'd like a tour of your facility.
You don't look Asian.
Well, I guess we'll just take
our millions of dongs elsewhere.
Wait, wait.
Let me get our general manager.
Peter, what the hell
do you expect to accomplish here?
Evidence, Brian.
I'm gonna find just the right piece
of incriminating evidence
to bring down this company.
Over here is a menu from our
first McBurgertown restaurant in 1952.
At that time, our value meal consisted of
a hamburger, a cup of coffee
and a Lucky Strike.
- Wow. How much did all that cost?
- Back in the '50s? One straw penny.
- A whole straw penny?
- Indeed. Follow me.
And in here,
we're test-marketing a new mascot,
Meaty, the Quick to Anger Clown.
Hey, kids!
Who likes McBurgertown burgers?
- I do!
- There was more to my question!
- We're still ironing that one out.
- Hey, what's in there?
Oh, I'm sorry. That's off-limits.
Now, if you'll excuse me for a second,
I have to go to the bathroom
for about 30 minutes,
as I eat a lot of meat.
Please give me your word
that you won't go in that door.
- Okay.
- Good. See you in a half hour.
- Peter, this is your chance!
- Brian, I gave him my word.
The hell with that.
Let's see what's behind this door.
My, God, what is this?
This must be
the McBurgertown slaughterhouse.
Sir, you are correct.
But in here, we call it DaCow.
- DaCow?
- DaCow,
except we spell the cow part c-o-w.
Like "cow." So it's kind of...
It's sort of a dark joke.
Yeah, yeah, it's a Holocaust joke.
That's really funny.
Unfortunately, life in a slaughterhouse
is no laughing matter.
They have killed a great many of us,
including my beloved wife.
Peter, this is it!
This is the evidence
you've been looking for!
If we can get you out of here,
would you be willing
to testify publicly about these atrocities?
Absolutely.
But how do you intend to escape?
You leave that to us. Come on.
Hey! There they are! After them!
Another Pleasant Valley Sunday
Charcoal burning everywhere
Here in status-symbol land
Hey, hey, what's up, Lucas?
What the hell's your problem?
Hey, Logan, what's going on?
What the hell is going on here?
Nothing, baby penis!
Well, yes, I have a baby...
Uh...
Well, for your information,
I don't want a big penis.
I think they're messy.
Well, you've effectively
ended my reign of coolness, haven't you?
You're a disgrace, you know that?
Hey, you're the one with the tiny penis.
You know, Connie, look.
You're right. I behaved like a fool.
And I apologize, but before I go,
could I maybe have one last kiss?
Well, I guess so.
Look! This girl is making out with a baby!
A nude baby!
Hey!
That's right. To hell with you all.
I am who I am.
Here comes the story of the hurricane
The man the authorities came to blame
For somethin' that he never done
Quiet, everybody, this is it.
The McBurgertown franchise
suffered a publicity setback today
from which it may not recover,
thanks to testimony
regarding its practices
by a very brave cow.
I have revealed to you today
these horrors in the hope
that you will see the need for change,
but always remember,
what I have done here today
is not a courageous act.
The courage lies with a man
who has the guts
to say no to a fast food restaurant
and eat a salad instead.
To say, '"I will eat this salad with pride.
I don't care if I look like a gay person. '"
So to all of you
salad-eating homosexuals,
I say thank you.
And thank you, Peter, for all you've done
to help expose this grave injustice.
- Where will you go now, Mr. Cow?
- I cannot stay here?
Peter said I could stay here.
Oh, gosh, yeah, I don't really see
how that's gonna work out.
Oh.
Well, as I said,
Peter just promised that I...
Yeah, I should stop you there.
I didn't really promise anything.
I just said,
"Maybe, if it was okay with Lois."
Boy, it seems like a real burden to me.
Well, this is pretty awkward.
Thank you for watching «Family Guy» on
www.FOX-fan.ru